I'm so agile.
I've tried so hard
to get this second life.
I can't succumb to fear.
I can't die like this!
Is it because my strength ability
has improved?
But... It's still stronger than me.
No. my attacks don't work.
What should I do?
It's too difficult alone.
There are no teammates or healers.
All I have is water and food.
If this goes on...
If only I had a weapon with magic power...
Weapon?
Inventory!
Though I don't know why
this is in my inventory.
Mr. Kim said this sword
cost him three million.
It's beyond my wildest dreams.
I can't think about that now.
I'll just use it.
My body stopped hurting.
As long as I have a weapon.
there's nothing to fear.
What? The sword won't come out!
Please. come out!
Your steel fangs seem genuine.
I finally got this sword.
Don't even try to damage it!
Upon closer inspection...
Compared to those things.
these beasts are nothing.
Eh. I'm level 2 now.
I never leveled up
when I completed daily quests.
I see. because this is actual combat.
My wounds just healed also because...
If I level up. all my abilities
will increase by one point?
A total of five points.
I only get three points from daily quests.
So leveling up through combat is faster.
How much will my abilities grow
with each point increase?
Even intelligence and perception
have been quantified.
Strength is the easiest to understand.
With only 32 points.
my movements became much lighter.
I'm only guessing.
But I think the higher the basic ability.
the more points I'll be able to get.
So... I really can become stronger.
But they are just five small magic beasts.
I may have got carried away.
They have no magic gems on them?
I have got an item instead of a magic gem?
Strange things are happening to me.
If I am controlled
by a system like a game.
will this dungeon and magic beasts
differ from the ones in reality?
Ah. I found the shop.
Purchase.
New players can't use it?
Sell.
Twenty gold coins.
How much would that be in cash?
But this dungeon is at most E-rank.
so 20 gold coins probably isn't much.
All right.
What should I do now?
I can't leave unless I defeat the boss.
It seems I could leave
once I get the teleportation stone.
but I have no idea where that is.
If this drags on. I'll be short of food.
Although it's an E-rank dungeon.
it's still so hard for me
to defeat the boss alone.
Wait... If I keep leveling up.
I might stand a chance.
Although it's possible
that I'll be dead before that.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I've died once after all.
I won't die that easily.
You don't die too quickly either.
If I kill you in an instant.
I'll feel really bad.
You have qualified as a hunter.
Now I can pay mom's medical bills.
If I could have another chance...
Let's...
Let's have a fierce battle.
As long as I'm alive.
I'll fight to the last moment.
As long as it makes me stronger...
I can abide by any rules!
That doesn't look good.
Can't the guild
come to deal with it quickly?
This sword is almost done for.
Weapons are just expendables after all.
No matter what weapon I get. it will
wear out after a few times in the dungeon.
However... It seems like the battle is over.
Thirty-four wolf fangs.
Two worn-out short swords.
A traveler's attire.
And...
The teleportation stone
that's easier to get than I imagined.
Should I return?
But.
perhaps there won't be a chance
to get stronger so easily again.
What will happen to this dungeon
if I use the teleportation stone?
Will it disappear?
Like a time-limited event in a game?
Regardless.
it seems like I am being toyed
with by some unknown force.
And I cannot escape.
Should I continue forward or turn back?
Yes. this is Lee Joohee.
Ah. you're from the Hunter's Association.
I'm really sorry about earlier.
That gate had a Dungeon Break?
Right around here?
It's all because I rejected him.
We're currently assembling
available hunters to deal with it.
But there's a serious shortage of healers.
I understand...
With each level up.
my battles with magic beasts
become easier.
The color denoting
the magic beast's name also changes.
I guess white means it's weaker than me.
Orange means it has the same level as me.
And red means it's stronger than me.
Lycan. which was initially marked red.
is marked white now.
This indicates I have become
much stronger.
Even so...
I still feel that I can't defeat
the one below with my current strength.
I don't know if it's because
my perception has improved.
I can clearly feel
that the monster below
is terrifying.
It seems I can no longer level up here.
If I keep fighting like this.
this sword probably won't hold up.
Are the stairs at this station so long?
It no longer looks like a station.
So fast!
The sword...
I've leveled up a lot.
but its name
is still in orange.
You're the boss here. right?
It's covered in scales.
This sword is useless against it.
Going bare-handed will be worse.
Its attacks are fast and heavy.
I can only try
to weaken its defense first.
But how can I pierce through
these thick scales?
If I took this hit head-on.
I would be dead.
I thought I had become a bit stronger...
Is it still not enough?
How strong do I have to be
to escape this life of constant ridicule?!
The Weakest Hunter of All Mankind.
Everyone has been calling you that lately.
Yes.
Damn it.
There are always people
who speak childishly.
Work hard and make them change their mind.
Yes.
I understand.
They gave me that nickname
because I was too weak.
I was looked down upon
I also felt useless.
As long as I'm strong enough...
One with overwhelming power
can naturally remain undefeated.
The weak are powerless before the strong.
The weak can only stand still.
trembling in fear.
People are looked down upon
because they are weak.
Even if they're knowledgeable.
smart. or considerate.
before the strong.
they will be betrayed.
Gentleness is meaningless.
So I must become stronger.
That's why I came here!
I...
I must become stronger.
Not enough.
Compared to that thing.
compared to the fear back then.
you have nothing to make me afraid!
I've put all my ability points
into strength.
With my current self...
I'm going to kill you!
Die!
It seems
I should have gotten a bit stronger.
Thanks to that. I got good stuff.
This dagger isn't made from bone
but from teeth?
Its power is twice that
of Mr. Kim's sword.
and it comes with paralysis
and bleeding effects.
By comparison.
this thing is too terrifying to use.
Anyway. I'll collect it for now.
Is it over?
Not a person in sight.
What time is it?
Hey!
How can you just walk in here?
Didn't you hear the announcement?
Announcement?
Don't play dumb with me...
Are you a hunter?
Yes. I am a hunter.
Sorry for being rude.
I'll take you to the site.
This way. please.
Ah. okay.
Has something happened?
Dungeon Break.
Did magic beasts get out?
Almost all of them have been killed.
Only a giant magic beast has been left.
I don't know if it's because
my perception has improved.
I can feel it.
That thing over there is the boss.
Please do not take photos.
This place is very dangerous.
Kill it quickly.
What if the land prices here drop?
All healers!
Please focus on healing the tanker!
I don't need you to tell me!
What are the fighters doing?
Why is it not weakening at all?
Its defense is just too strong.
We have few mages among us.
Excuse me. let us through!
Is it because it's a temporary team?
They don't work well together.
Their ranks are too low.
It should be eight E-rank hunters
and one D-rank hunter.
And because that tanker is D-rank.
it became a prolonged battle
as no one could deliver a fatal blow.
As for the healers. are they
two D-rank healers and one B-rank healer?
Hey. Miss!
Hurry up and heal them!
Aren't you a B-rank healer?
What are you dazed about?
Yes.
Damn it. pull yourself together.
She still hasn't gotten over it
after a week?
It's no surprise.
After all. I also...
No.
This is a D-rank boss.
It's weaker than the one I just defeated.
We'll get wiped out if this continues!
We can't defeat it
without a high-rank hunter!
As long as I can break its defense.
I can defeat it!
I'll give it the most powerful hit.
Take this!
Good. its defense is broken.
We can defeat it.
We did it.
We defeated it!
All attacks were ineffective against it.
Why were we able to break its defense?
Our attacks had no effect.
It was something that flew over...
A Boss Golem that remained unscathed
under the attack of a dozen hunters
was defeated by this thing?
- Sorry.
- Yes.
Who threw this?
Oh. it was the hunter over there...
Huh?
- He was just here.
- Such terrifying destructive power.
Is he a high-rank hunter?
I didn't expect to take it down
with a single strike.
Perhaps that Golem
was running out of vitality anyway.
Jinwoo...